http://50dollarbrochures.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content  December 11, 2020
HomeAboutContactPrivacy Policy
HomeAboutContactPrivacy Policy
Search for:
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy for http://50dollarbrochures.com If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@50dollarbrochures.com. At http://50dollarbrochures.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://50dollarbrochures.com and how it is used.Log FilesLike many other Web sites, http://50dollarbrochures.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.Cookies and Web Beaconshttp://50dollarbrochures.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://50dollarbrochures.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. http://50dollarbrochures.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://50dollarbrochures.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Search for:
Recent Posts Exactly why Online Gambling is Growing Even in a Recession 23893573 The very best 10 Things to See and Do in Nan, Thailand You have to know About Nudes On the net Gambling May Be Lower Off By New Legislation 23445234 About three Common Methods For Net Files ExtractionRecent CommentsA WordPress Commenter on Hello world!ArchivesDecember 2020November 2020October 2020September 2020CategoriesUncategorizedMetaLog inEntries feedComments feedWordPress.org
